<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Orlando Real Estate Video Blog with teamFREDA</title>
    <description>Our mission at teamFREDA is to be your best resource for Orlando real estate advice. Whether you are a buyer, seller, or investor, our team of professionals can answer any questions you might have about real estate. If you are looking to buy or sell a home, you can get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The teamFREDA, your professional Orlando Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <link>localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 16:10:45 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 16:10:45 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Join Us for Our Upcoming Live Event: &quot;eXp Explained&quot;</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/0P1yiMEsr8M?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your home is your biggest financial investment. Whoever you hire to help sell it needs to be qualified for the job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the state of Florida, anybody can get their real estate license within a week or two. All you need to do is take a three-day class and sit for a state exam.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Because the barrier of entry into the business is so low, everybody knows someone around here who has a real estate license.&lt;/strong&gt; Maybe it’s a friend, a family member, or a neighbor. This might be the first person you think of when it comes to real estate and you might be ready to hire them on the spot, but you shouldn’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For most of us, our home is our biggest financial investment. You want to be sure you’re putting that asset in the right hands before you hire somebody to do the job. I’ve worked with expired listings a lot and one of the common threads I’ve seen is the fact that most of these people hired an agent who was a friend or family member and didn’t interview anybody else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=YOU SHOULD INTERVIEW AT LEAST THREE DIFFERENT AGENTS FOR THE JOB.%20localhost:4000/join-us-for-our-upcoming-live-event-exp.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“YOU SHOULD INTERVIEW AT LEAST THREE DIFFERENT AGENTS FOR THE JOB.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of the day, selling your home is a business transaction. If someone isn’t owning up to their responsibility as an agent, you shouldn’t hesitate to fire them. &lt;strong&gt;If it’s a good friend or family member that you hire, the hesitation will definitely be there.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s why I think you need to interview at least three different agents for the job of selling your home before you hire one. Interview that friend or family member you know, but also interview somebody who has a proven track record and great reviews online. It will make your ultimate decision a lot easier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I’d love to interview for the job of helping you buy or sell a home.&lt;/strong&gt; If you have any questions for me or want to know how I can help you achieve your real estate goals, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 12:52:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>localhost:4000/join-us-for-our-upcoming-live-event-exp.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">localhost:4000/join-us-for-our-upcoming-live-event-exp.html</guid>
        
        <category>Orlando Real Estate Agent</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Helpful Guide for Picking a Real Estate Agent</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/kdt-SBQlFjg?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your home is your biggest financial investment. Whoever you hire to help sell it needs to be qualified for the job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the state of Florida, anybody can get their real estate license within a week or two. All you need to do is take a three-day class and sit for a state exam.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Because the barrier of entry into the business is so low, everybody knows someone around here who has a real estate license.&lt;/strong&gt; Maybe it’s a friend, a family member, or a neighbor. This might be the first person you think of when it comes to real estate and you might be ready to hire them on the spot, but you shouldn’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For most of us, our home is our biggest financial investment. You want to be sure you’re putting that asset in the right hands before you hire somebody to do the job. I’ve worked with expired listings a lot and one of the common threads I’ve seen is the fact that most of these people hired an agent who was a friend or family member and didn’t interview anybody else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=YOU SHOULD INTERVIEW AT LEAST THREE DIFFERENT AGENTS FOR THE JOB.%20localhost:4000/a-helpful-guide-for-picking-real-estate.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“YOU SHOULD INTERVIEW AT LEAST THREE DIFFERENT AGENTS FOR THE JOB.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of the day, selling your home is a business transaction. If someone isn’t owning up to their responsibility as an agent, you shouldn’t hesitate to fire them. &lt;strong&gt;If it’s a good friend or family member that you hire, the hesitation will definitely be there.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s why I think you need to interview at least three different agents for the job of selling your home before you hire one. Interview that friend or family member you know, but also interview somebody who has a proven track record and great reviews online. It will make your ultimate decision a lot easier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I’d love to interview for the job of helping you buy or sell a home.&lt;/strong&gt; If you have any questions for me or want to know how I can help you achieve your real estate goals, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 13:42:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>localhost:4000/a-helpful-guide-for-picking-real-estate.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">localhost:4000/a-helpful-guide-for-picking-real-estate.html</guid>
        
        <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Youre Invited to Our Next HUD Training Event</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/x5tCsLBF3es?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re hosting an upcoming HUD training. We hope you’ll join us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m here to invite you to our next HUD agent training on March 14 from 11:30 a.m. to 1 p.m. It will be held over at the office of our friends at Quality Title &amp;amp; Escrow in their Kissimmee. We will cover the entire process, from build submission all the way through closing. All the questions you wish you had answers to will be answered. We’ll have lunch for you as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=ALL OF YOUR QUESTIONS WILL BE ANSWERED.%20localhost:4000/youre-invited-to-our-next-hud-training.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“ALL OF YOUR QUESTIONS WILL BE ANSWERED.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ll have mortgage, title, and real estate experts there to answer all your questions. RSVP by sending an email to info@fredarealtyorlando.com today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions for us, don’t hesitate to reach out by phone or email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 14:36:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>localhost:4000/youre-invited-to-our-next-hud-training.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">localhost:4000/youre-invited-to-our-next-hud-training.html</guid>
        
        <category>Team Freda HUD Training</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Rising Interest Rates Impact Your Plans to Buy</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/hKLVrmMWuQ4?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rising interest rates may put buying a new home out of reach. I’ll explain why today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently came across an article about how mortgage interest rates are on the rise. I’ve read articles like this in the past, but this article was a little different.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inflation is firming because employers are under pressure to increase their wages.&lt;/strong&gt; What does that mean if you plan on purchasing a property?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rates have been hovering below 4%, but today they are up a little, at 4.04% for a 30-year, fixed-rate mortgage. This is still a relatively low, reasonable rate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=THE PROJECTED RATE INCREASES AND HOME APPRECIATION MAY PUSH MANY BUYERS OUT OF THE MARKET.%20localhost:4000/how-rising-interest-rates-impact-your.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“THE PROJECTED RATE INCREASES AND HOME APPRECIATION MAY PUSH MANY BUYERS OUT OF THE MARKET.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Still, with rates projected to increase over the course of 2018, along with a projected 4% rise in overall home values this year, &lt;strong&gt;many potential buyers may soon find themselves pushed out of the market in terms of affordability.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are thinking about securing a mortgage, you may want to get started sooner rather than later in order to take advantage of today’s relatively low interest rates and market opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you need any help with preparing for that process, or have any questions regarding buying a new home, just give us a call or send us an email. We would be happy to help you!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 16:07:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>localhost:4000/how-rising-interest-rates-impact-your.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">localhost:4000/how-rising-interest-rates-impact-your.html</guid>
        
        <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Join eXp Realty for the Opportunity of a Lifetime</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/StXF8_p6b8s?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking for a model that will promote your team’s growth, I truly recommend that you consider joining with eXp Realty. In the best way, you won’t see the industry the same way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am so excited to announce that &lt;strong&gt;we are moving from our independent brokerage model to eXp Realty,&lt;/strong&gt; and even more excited to be working once again with the National Association of Expert Advisors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I am joined by Jay Kinder, one of the co-founders of the NAEA, to talk about his background, his role in the NAEA, and how that ties in with eXp Realty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jay is a lifelong agent who has been in the business for 20 years since his father introduced him to it through his ownership of Coldwell Banker. In his career, Jay has racked up a number of achievements, such as:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• In his peak year, he sold 531 homes.
• He has sold over 4,000 homes in total.
• He was named the No. 2 agent in the world by Coldwell Banker in 2007.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jay has since channeled his experience and expertise into training real estate agents on how to build a successful business. One of the challenges that he faced in building his own business was its sustainability, especially in terms of developing a working team model and maintaining its profitability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throughout the past 10 years, Jay has worked towards expanding his partnerships across the country, asking the question, “How can we all put our fires together to make one big fire?” In other words, how can we all work together to create one great company? Until he joined with eXp Realty, he hadn’t found a platform to do that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before joining, he had heard of eXp, but wasn’t really sure of what it was, so he discounted it. It wasn’t until someone had him watch one of their webinars that he took a closer look. &lt;strong&gt;He found that eXp provided the platform to develop a stronger team and a stronger business.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though he’s only been with eXp for about two and a half months, Jay has already had the most fun he’s ever had in his real estate career.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Freda Team is also excited to join the movement. We’ve been an independent brokerage for 13 years and have been approached by different models and companies. It wasn’t until Jay Kinder announced via Facebook Live that he was making the change that I saw what I couldn’t unsee. After seeing the webinar and looking at the model eXp provided, I realized that &lt;strong&gt;it solves a lot of the problems we’ve experienced over the years in terms of growing or retracting a team.&lt;/strong&gt; It took me a couple months to make the jump, and now I’m just upset that I didn’t do it sooner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=ONCE YOU COME TO UNDERSTAND THE EXP MODEL, YOU’LL REALIZE THAT IT’S SIMPLY BETTER.%20localhost:4000/join-exp-realty-for-opportunity-of.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“ONCE YOU COME TO UNDERSTAND THE EXP MODEL, YOU’LL REALIZE THAT IT’S SIMPLY BETTER.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that we’ve made the switch, we can’t wait to show more people the agent-centric model, technology, and training eXp provides. In addition, partnering up with the NAEA and having the experience of people like Jay Kinder in our network to promote the growth of new agents is very exciting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There are many reasons to make the jump to eXp Realty.&lt;/strong&gt; There are many amazing components to their business model, they’re publicly traded, they offer revenue sharing, and there is so much room for growth and opportunity. There may be only 7,000 or so agents in the network at the moment, but since they’re already adding 250 agents per week, I truly believe that it will one day become the biggest real estate company in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though you may feel satisfied with your independent brokerage now, &lt;strong&gt;once you come to understand the eXp model, you’ll realize that it’s simply better.&lt;/strong&gt; Why try to reinvent the wheel? With the new technology that’s available, we can take our services to a higher level and network not only with people in our area but throughout the country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We all get value from helping agents grow their business, but many agents at independent brokerages don’t have viable retirement strategies. &lt;strong&gt;The agent ownership and the stock program that eXp has available could make you very wealthy&lt;/strong&gt; and set you up for a very comfortable retirement plan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Real estate agents are entrepreneurs. When you take the opportunities provided by eXp and add them to your own business model, where you can get passive income simply for informing people about the benefits they stand to gain when they work with eXp, it disrupts the traditional sense of recruiting. I have the financial incentive to ensure that you and your team are successful. When you factor in all of the great teams that are joining the network, we are all aligned with each other to promote growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;With all of us working together, anything is possible.&lt;/strong&gt; I can’t overstate how much I would recommend that anyone who is in search of a better model for their team to invest 60 or so minutes of their time to watching the eXp Realty webinar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about what you can gain from working with eXp, feel free to reach out. I’d be glad to answer any questions you have.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 16:40:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>localhost:4000/join-exp-realty-for-opportunity-of.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">localhost:4000/join-exp-realty-for-opportunity-of.html</guid>
        
        <category>teamFREDA</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Want to Learn How to Successfully Close and Sell HUD Homes?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/fGEKsc7Iuz0?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re hosting an event this December that will teach you how to successfully close and sell HUD homes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are officially invited to our upcoming Realtor HUD lunch-and-learn training session.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this event, we’ll cover all the details from the contract-to-close process. It will take place on December 7 from 11:30 a.m. to 1 p.m. at 665 West Warren Avenue, Longwood, Florida 32750.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=WE WANT TO GIVE YOU A QUICK TOUR TO SHOW YOU EXACTLY HOW OUR TEAM IS STRUCTURED.%20localhost:4000/learn-how-to-sell-and-close-homes-at.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“WE WANT TO GIVE YOU A QUICK TOUR TO SHOW YOU EXACTLY HOW OUR TEAM IS STRUCTURED.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To RSVP, you can either leave a comment below or call us at (407) 513-4724.&lt;/strong&gt; We look forward to seeing you, and it will be well worth your time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the meantime, if you have any questions, don’t hesitate to reach out to us. We’d be happy to speak with you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 13:54:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>localhost:4000/learn-how-to-sell-and-close-homes-at.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">localhost:4000/learn-how-to-sell-and-close-homes-at.html</guid>
        
        <category>Orlando HUD Homes</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Meet the Members of teamFREDA</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/2n3DGghe4Ds?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today we’ll be going on a quick tour around the office, introducing you to key members of teamFREDA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re here at our office in Longwood today, and we wanted to give you a quick tour to show you exactly how our team is structured.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On this tour, we will introduce you to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;◘ &lt;strong&gt;Karen Sierra, our listing coordinator.&lt;/strong&gt; Karen works with the sellers to help them create the best marketing campaign to get their property sold. She also manages the REO (real estate owned), bank-owned, and HUD (housing and urban development) properties, with the same goal of marketing them to sell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=WE WANT TO GIVE YOU A QUICK TOUR TO SHOW YOU EXACTLY HOW OUR TEAM IS STRUCTURED.%20localhost:4000/meet-members-of-team-freda.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“WE WANT TO GIVE YOU A QUICK TOUR TO SHOW YOU EXACTLY HOW OUR TEAM IS STRUCTURED.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;◘ &lt;strong&gt;Cory&lt;/strong&gt;, our inside sales agent who works with expired listings and FBSOs. Cory books appointments for the listing specialist, as well as fielding calls to the sink database—the database of buyers that registered on our website, looking for information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;◘ &lt;strong&gt;Tara, our buyer specialist.&lt;/strong&gt; Today, she’s calling all past clients that we’re trying to schedule showings for who we haven’t been able to, as well as reaching out to those who’ve emailed her previously looking for additional information on search criteria for a particular home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;◘ &lt;strong&gt;Matthew&lt;/strong&gt;, one of our team leaders. Matthew talks a little bit about how each team member fits into the mold at teamFREDA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;◘ &lt;strong&gt;Traci McCain&lt;/strong&gt;, our director of development and training. Traci helps design and implement the training processes, as well as with mentoring and training the new agents. As a Realtor herself, she also prospects and works her own deals. Additionally, she oversees and manages all transactions. When a client goes from contract to close, we take that workload off the agent’s plate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the full tour, watch the video above.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 15:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>localhost:4000/meet-members-of-team-freda.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">localhost:4000/meet-members-of-team-freda.html</guid>
        
        <category>teamFREDA</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Where Is the Best Place to Find HUD Homes?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/2yYw41ObXCA?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re thinking about selling your home, our 151-step marketing system can help you sell quickly and for top dollar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can help you get your home sold quickly and for top dollar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our 151-step marketing system has allowed us to sell over 500 homes in the last three years throughout central Florida.&lt;/strong&gt; We want to put this system to work for you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=WE WILL WORK WITH YOU TO LAY OUT A STRATEGIC PLAN TO GET YOUR HOUSE SOLD.%20localhost:4000/where-is-best-place-to-find-hud-homes.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“WE WILL WORK WITH YOU TO LAY OUT A STRATEGIC PLAN TO GET YOUR HOUSE SOLD.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Getting started is simple. First, schedule an equity consultation with us. From there, we will work with you to lay out a strategic plan to get your house sold for the most money in the least amount of time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Give us a call or send us an email today to schedule your consultation or ask any other questions you may have. We look forward to hearing from you!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 14:49:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>localhost:4000/where-is-best-place-to-find-hud-homes.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">localhost:4000/where-is-best-place-to-find-hud-homes.html</guid>
        
        <category>Orlando HUD Homes</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How the Latest Decrease in Rates Affects You</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/2yYw41ObXCA?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re thinking about selling your home, our 151-step marketing system can help you sell quickly and for top dollar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can help you get your home sold quickly and for top dollar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our 151-step marketing system has allowed us to sell over 500 homes in the last three years throughout central Florida.&lt;/strong&gt; We want to put this system to work for you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=WE WILL WORK WITH YOU TO LAY OUT A STRATEGIC PLAN TO GET YOUR HOUSE SOLD.%20localhost:4000/how-latest-decrease-in-rates-affects-you.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“WE WILL WORK WITH YOU TO LAY OUT A STRATEGIC PLAN TO GET YOUR HOUSE SOLD.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Getting started is simple. First, schedule an equity consultation with us. From there, we will work with you to lay out a strategic plan to get your house sold for the most money in the least amount of time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Give us a call or send us an email today to schedule your consultation or ask any other questions you may have. We look forward to hearing from you!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 13:35:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>localhost:4000/how-latest-decrease-in-rates-affects-you.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">localhost:4000/how-latest-decrease-in-rates-affects-you.html</guid>
        
        <category>Central Florida Market Update</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Put Our Home-Selling Success to Work for You </title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/2yYw41ObXCA?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re thinking about selling your home, our 151-step marketing system can help you sell quickly and for top dollar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can help you get your home sold quickly and for top dollar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our 151-step marketing system has allowed us to sell over 500 homes in the last three years throughout central Florida.&lt;/strong&gt; We want to put this system to work for you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=WE WILL WORK WITH YOU TO LAY OUT A STRATEGIC PLAN TO GET YOUR HOUSE SOLD.%20localhost:4000/put-our-home-selling-success-to-work.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“WE WILL WORK WITH YOU TO LAY OUT A STRATEGIC PLAN TO GET YOUR HOUSE SOLD.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Getting started is simple. First, schedule an equity consultation with us. From there, we will work with you to lay out a strategic plan to get your house sold for the most money in the least amount of time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Give us a call or send us an email today to schedule your consultation or ask any other questions you may have. We look forward to hearing from you!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 10:55:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>localhost:4000/put-our-home-selling-success-to-work.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">localhost:4000/put-our-home-selling-success-to-work.html</guid>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
